Andrew Moses

Full Stack Web Developer focused on creating unique, accessible, and user-friendly applications. Experienced team lead with a demonstrated history of success in leadership within the financial services and healthcare industries. Lifelong learner obsessed with finding a better way, taking on new challenges, and solving problems.

CONTACT

Location: Tempe, Arizona 85283

Phone: (480) 612-5250

Email: andrewmosesdrive@gmail.com

GitHub: http://bit.ly/2WyYNU0
Portfolio: https://bit.ly/34vTvwU
LinkedIn: https://bit.ly/3hcZY5e

EXPERIENCE

DevCore/Quicken Loans — Trainer, Team Captain | 2019 - Present

Leads new team members through intensive training on all areas of knowledge related to their future careers. Mentors and coaches new trainers as they develop their training skills.

Donor Network of Arizona — Lead Recovery Coordinator | 2011 - 2019

Directed teams of 3-5 individuals in highly adaptive and situations with heavy time restrictions. Trained new and existing staff in all clinical positions and medical record/suitability review via EMR.

PROJECTS

Management ERP - GitHub: https://bit.ly/3mvrwDS

Full stack enterprise resource planning application built with three other developers using Node, Express-Handlebars, and Sequelize ORM. Deployed through Heroku.

Team Generator CLI - GitHub: http://bit.ly/2WyZq8I

Command line interface application for team template generation. Created with Node, Inquirer, and Jest for testing.

Fitness Tracker - GitHub: http://bit.ly/3h5rBwL | Deployment: https://bit.ly/3mATNJf

Full stack application for creating, tracking, and logging workouts with persistence. Built with MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, and Node. Deployed via Heroku.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

React, Amazon Web Services/Amplify, JavaScript, Node, Express, HTML5, CSS3, Handlebars, MySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose, JawsDB, GraphQL, jQuery, Lodash, Materialize, Bootstrap, Webpack, Babel, Progressive Web Applications, Visual Studio, Git, Slack, Chrome DevTools, NPM, Heroku, CRUD, Agile Methodology, Unit Testing

CORE COMPETENCIES

Problem solving, Planning/Operations, Research

EDUCATION

University of Arizona — Full Stack Web Development Certificate 2019 Scottsdale Community College — Associates Degree 2016 - 2018